

Contact

Bhubaneswar, 751024

977771132

santosini.bisoyi80@gmail.com

Skills

Programming Languages

- Node js
- Python
- Java Script
- React Js

Technology

- · Elastic Search
- Pubsub
- redis

Frameworks/Platforms

- Express is
- React is

Database

- Cassandra(CQL)
- MySQL
- PgSQL
- MongoDB
- BigQuery

Tools

- PyCharm
- Visual Studio Code
- GitHub , GitLab
- Jira

Web Server

- XAMPP
- MySQL Workbench

santosini Bisoyi

Summary

A software development professional with experience of 2.5 years. Currently associated with IServeU Technology Pvt. Ltd. as a Software Engineer Trainee, in (Node.js) Developer in a Fintech sector. Inquisitive to learn new technologies with true commitment of adaptability.

Experience

Software Developer

IServeU Technology Pvt. Ltd | Bhubaneswar, India | Jun 2022 - Current

- Developing and maintaining server-side applications using Node.js. Writing reusable, testable, and efficient code. Developed real-time features using advanced technologies.
- Developed and integrated middleware components for tasks such as logging, error handling, and request validation. Designed and implemented scalable and efficient server-side logic using Node.is.

Junior Software Engineer

Cocypher IT Solutions Pvt. Ltd | Bhubaneswar, India | Oct 2021 - May 2022

- Develop and maintain web application using MERN stack. Proficient in frontend technology React
 JS to build user interface. Backend Node js for creating API.
- Knowledge of database design implementation and optimization using mongo DB / MySQL workbench .Created technical documentation, sharing knowledge, ideas and solutions with wider development team.

Software Developer

IntelCrop Solutions Pvt. Ltd | Bhubaneswar, India | Oct 2020 - Sep 2021

- Kept up-to-date on the latest website design trends to stay relevant in competitive markets.
- Improved user experience by implementing changes in response to A/B testing results.

IT Traineer

Kiit University | Bhubaneswar, India | Aug 2016 - Jul 2020

- Performing role-specific training on tools and programs each student uses daily.
- Train new employees on proper use of hardware and software

Education

KIIT University

Bhubaneswar, Odisha

M.Tech: 7.8 CGPA

2016

Computer Science &

Information Security

KIIT University

Bhubaneswar, Odisha

B.Tech: 6.6 CGPA

2013

Computer Science Engineering

Kalinga Polytechnic

Bhubaneswar

Diploma: 70%

2010

Computer Science Engineering

Govt Girls High School , Unit-

8

Bhubaneswar

Certificate of Higher

Education: 46%

2007

Project Handled

AXIS FD Service, IServeU Tech.Pvt. Ltd, Odisha.(12/23 - till date)

- · Client :- AXIS
- Description :- Provide Fixed Deposit service to the customer. My role as a Backend Developer.

Kotak 2Wheeler Insurance, IServeU Tech.Pvt. Ltd, Odisha.(6/23 - 11/23)

- Client :- Kotak
- **Description**:- Provide Insurance service to the customer. My role as a Backend Developer.

<u>Livlong Health Insurance</u>, <u>IServeU Tech. Pvt. Ltd, Odisha, India</u> (01/23 - 5/23)

- Client :- End Consumers
- **Description:** It provides Family Health insurance policy for customers. My role as a Backend Developer.

<u>Virtual Account</u>, <u>IServeU Tech. Pvt. Ltd, Odisha, India (06/22 - 12/22)</u>

- · Client:- AXIS Bank, FINO Bank, IPPB
- Description:- It provides virtual account application to retailers who use this product to register
 new account for consumers at Bank virtually and provide platform to existing customer to access
 their account virtually. My role as a Backend Developer.

<u>driEV Two Wheeler, Cocypher IT Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Odisha, India (10/21 - 05/22)</u>

- · Client: driEV electric vehicle company.
- Description:- driEV is an Electric Vehicle bike sharing company. This project aimed at creating website for a cab aggregation. Starting from the frontend, database and backend. The frontend part we design as per client Figma Design using React MUI. After that design the Database as per client's need using MySQL Workbench. Then create API as per the database. Then design Admin panel UI then complete the Admin Panel fetching API call. Then the whole booking system of the driEV project. My role as a Full Stack Developer.